showcasecinemas.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Showcase Cinemas

National Amusements, Inc., its subsidiaries and affiliates, which operate under the Showcase Cinemas brand (collectively, “Showcase Cinemas” or “we”) values its relationship with patrons, members and clients, and is committed to responsible information handling practices.  
This privacy policy only applies to information collected from you by Showcase Cinemas when you visit the Showcase Cinemas websites where this privacy policy is posted (“Sites”), register for information or content Showcase Cinemas makes available (“Data”) at our Sites, through your download and use of any mobile application, including widgets, shortcuts or user interface (collectively the, “Applications”) that Showcase Cinemas may make publicly available, and through your electronic communications with Showcase Cinemas. This privacy policy does not apply to any information collected by Showcase Cinemas through any other means. The “Showcase Subscribe” Online Privacy Policy describes the practices specific to that Application.  
Although Showcase Cinemas makes available Applications, and a number of Sites with unique Data, services and offerings, each Showcase Cinemas Site and Application shares the following privacy philosophies and principles:  
• Providing you with notice of Showcase Cinemas’ information practices;  
• Giving you choices about how Showcase Cinemas will use information collected from you;  
• Providing you with the opportunity to update or correct your personally identifiable information;  
• Using information security safeguards;  
• Limiting the sharing of your information with other parties;  
• Committing to complying with applicable privacy requirements; and  
• Providing you with means to contact Showcase Cinemas about privacy-related issues.  
The following privacy policy describes how Showcase Cinemas collects, uses, and protects information collected from you during your visit to showcasecinemas.com, and from your download and use of an Application. 

**What Information Does Showcase Cinemas Collect?**  
When you visit Showcase Cinemas’ Site or use an Application, you will provide anonymous information that Showcase Cinemas collects and you may voluntarily share personal information with Showcase Cinemas.

**Anonymous or Non-Personally Identifiable Information.**  
Showcase Cinemas automatically collects information from you when you visit its Sites, such as the search engine you used to access the Sites, the previous websites you visited, the websites or advertisements you view or select, the type of Internet browser you use, the computer operating system you use, and your computer’s IP address. Showcase Cinemas may also collect information concerning your movie preferences, such as the movies for which you purchase tickets and the theaters in which you view those movies.  
The Applications may collect certain information automatically, such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device’s unique device ID, the IP address of your mobile device, the operating system for your mobile device, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use the Application.  
The Showcase Cinemas Sites and Applications permit you to search for movie information, movie show times, and the Showcase Cinemas theaters closest to you. If you use such location-enabled parts of the Applications or similar functionality available at the Showcase Cinemas Sites, you may be sending Showcase Cinemas location information. This information may reveal your precise location, such as GPS signals sent by your mobile device, or your approximate location, from your IP address or the ID of your mobile device or when you submit a zip code or partial address for movie information.

**Personally Identifiable Information.**  
Personally identifiable information is information that identifies you, such as your name, postal address, wired and mobile telephone number, gender, birth date, e-mail address, payment method, movie preferences, favorite movies, and other information once it is associated with your personally identifiable information. We may ask you to provide personally identifiable information when you create an online account, sign up for the Starpass loyalty program, register for the Showcase Subscribe membership program, download and register an Application, purchase products or services, participate in a sweepstakes, promotion or survey, contact Showcase Cinemas with a question or concern, or participate in other activities when you visit a Showcase Cinemas Site or use an Application. If you choose to use the Facebook Connect feature or similar features in connection with your account or Application, you are asking the social network provider to share your profile information with Showcase Cinemas. Showcase Cinemas will collect, store and use all information it receives from the social network provider about you in accordance with this privacy policy. Moreover, if you are a member of another social network or service, and you authorize Showcase Cinemas to associate your account or Application with that network or service, Showcase Cinemas will gather information about your online behavior at the Showcase Cinemas Site or through your use of the Applications, and will associate that information with personally identifiable information Showcase Cinemas already has about you and use it on-line or offline, in accordance with this Policy.

**How Does Showcase Cinemas Use Information?**  
Showcase Cinemas uses personally identifiable information for the purpose for which you provided it, such as to fulfill your request for products, services or Data, to process and administer your contest or sweepstakes entry and to activate and maintain your online and/or Applications accounts. We do not collect personal information from children (individuals 12 or under). All personal information that we collect is submitted voluntarily to allow visitors of the appropriate age to enter contests, participate in loyalty or related programs, make purchases or subscribe to receive email. Registration may include contact information (name, email, age, postal address and telephone number) and demographic information (zip code or favorite theater) to allow us to ship prizes or purchases.  If you wish to opt out of any offer or program, visit the opt-out area on our Sites, e-mail us at customer_service@national-amusements.com, or contact us at: National Amusements, Inc., 846 University Avenue, PO Box 9108, Norwood, Massachusetts 02062-9108 Attn: Customer Service.  
Showcase Cinemas combines anonymous usage information collected from your visit to a Showcase Cinemas Site or use of an Application with that of other users to determine which features and areas of the Site or Application are most popular. By collecting and analyzing this information, Showcase Cinemas can improve its Sites and Applications. This aggregated information does not contain information personally associated with you.  
Showcase Cinemas may also update and supplement personally identifiable information collected from you with other information that Showcase Cinemas obtains from third parties or from Showcase Cinemas’ subsidiaries and affiliates. If Showcase Cinemas associates information obtained from affiliates and subsidiaries or other third parties with personally identifiable information collected under this policy, Showcase Cinemas will treat the acquired information like information Showcase Cinemas has acquired itself.

**Does Showcase Cinemas Share or Transfer the Information Users Provide?**

**Sharing among the Showcase Cinemas Family of Companies.**  
Showcase Cinemas may combine personally identifiable information collected by a Showcase Cinemas affiliate or subsidiary with personally identifiable information Showcase Cinemas has collected. Showcase Cinemas may share your personally identifiable information with Showcase Cinemas’ subsidiaries or affiliates to provide you with entertainment news, e-mail offers, and movie ticket savings, and to let you know about other Showcase Cinemas’ products and services that may be of interest to you, and other business purposes.

**Sharing with Third Parties.**  
Showcase Cinemas shares aggregated information with its third party service providers to assist Showcase Cinemas with collecting demographic information and improving its Sites and Applications.   
Showcase Cinemas uses third parties to assist it in providing services, fulfilling orders, Data and information requests, to improve your experience with the Applications and on Showcase Cinemas’ Sites and for other business purposes. Showcase Cinemas will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties for these administrative purposes; however, these third parties will not contact you directly. If you wish to opt out of any offer or program, visit the opt-out area on our website, e-mail us at customer_service@national-amusements.com, or contact us at: National Amusements, Inc., 846 University Avenue, PO Box 9108, Norwood, MA 02062-9108 Attn: Customer Service.  
Moreover, if you are a member of a social network service, such as Facebook, Google+, or similar website where you have authorized them to share your information with Showcase Cinemas (e.g., use of Facebook Connect) or to gather information about your online behavior on Showcase Cinemas’ Site or use of an Application (for instance, to notify your friends that you have reviewed a movie or bought tickets), including participation in any behavioral reporting program that the social network may operate on or off of the social network website, those third parties may gather information about your online behavior on Showcase Cinemas’ Site or use of an Application, and Showcase Cinemas may share information regarding your activities on a Showcase Cinemas Site or use of an Application with those third parties as authorized by you, and they may associate that information with personally identifiable information they already have about you (such as your Facebook Profile) and use it to improve the social network site or services, or for other purposes.  
When Showcase Cinemas uses agents, contractors or other third parties to perform services on its behalf, Showcase Cinemas will require that they protect your personally identifiable information in accordance with this Policy. We strongly urge you to ensure that you are comfortable with the privacy policies of any social network site or other website that you authorize to gather information from Showcase Cinemas because the privacy policies of those websites will govern the use of your personally identifiable information once Showcase Cinemas has transmitted it.

**Disclosure Required by Law.**  
From time to time, Showcase Cinemas may be required to share your personally identifiable information with law enforcement or other governmental agencies in response to a court order, subpoena, government investigation, or as otherwise required by law. Showcase Cinemas also reserves the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that Showcase Cinemas, in good faith, believes to be unlawful. Showcase Cinemas also may share certain personally identifiable information when it believes that such sharing is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and itself.

**Disclosure as a part of a Business Transaction.**  
In the event Showcase Cinemas or any of its assets are acquired by a third party, personal information acquired by Showcase Cinemas may be one of the assets transferred. As a part of any such transaction, Showcase Cinemas will treat your information as an asset and transfer it to the purchaser.

**Transfer of Information.**  
If you reside outside of the United States, such as in the European Union or elsewhere, please be aware that any information you provide to Showcase Cinemas at www.showcasecinemas.com or through an Application will be transferred to and processed in the United States. If you do not wish for Showcase Cinemas to transfer your personally identifiable information into the United States, do not submit it to Showcase Cinemas. If you provide Showcase Cinemas with your personally identifiable information, Showcase Cinemas will treat your submission of that information as your consent to allow Showcase Cinemas to transfer it to the United States. Any personally identifiable information that Showcase Cinemas collects from you at www.showcasecinemas.com or through an Application will be treated in accordance with this privacy policy.

**How Does Showcase Cinemas Secure Users’ Personal Information?**  
Showcase Cinemas uses several encryption methods, such as Secure Sockets Layer technology for the transmission of data, and other measures to ensure that the personally identifiable information you submit to Showcase Cinemas through your use of a Showcase Cinemas Site or Application, is secure. Showcase Cinemas takes reasonable measures to ensure that your personally identifiable information remains secure. Showcase Cinemas also maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards guard personally identifiable information. Please be aware that, although Showcase Cinemas endeavors to maintain the security of information in its possession, no security system is capable of preventing all security breaches.

**Cookies and Other Technologies**  
The Showcase Cinemas Sites and Applications are designed to use cookies to collect and store temporary session information about visitor preferences. This is done in order to recognize users, provide personalization, optimize performance of the Showcase Cinemas Sites and Applications, and collect traffic data (e.g., number of visitors to the Showcase Cinemas Sites, frequency of visits or use, length of visit, and the use made, or the feature, function or advertisement selected). Showcase Cinemas may also uses cookies to conduct polls, surveys and contests to limit multiple responses and registrations. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can adjust their settings to refuse cookies or to alert them when cookies are being sent. If you choose to reject all cookies or similar technology, they may be unable to use much of the functionality of the Showcase Cinemas Sites and Applications, such as polls, surveys or contests.  
The Applications may also use various technologies (such as flash cookies, HTML5 software, local storage, and mini-databases) to track your web browsing activity conducted through the Applications and may store such information on your mobile device. Many mobile devices have this technology pre-loaded or incorporated in the web browser, or the technology may be included in the mobile application you download and use on your device. Please consult your device documentation on how to manage the information gathering and storage aspects of this technology.  
Unless we associate information that we gather through use of technology with your personally identifiable information, we will NOT treat such information as personally identifiable information.

**Can Other Parties Obtain Information From Me When I Visit a Showcase Cinemas Site?**  
Showcase Cinemas’ Site may contain links to websites that are owned and operated by third parties. You should be aware that when you click on these third-party links, you may deploy technology (such as cookies or web beacons), which third parties may use to identify some of your preferences or to recognize you if you have previously been to their website or otherwise had contact with them. Certain activities on Showcase Cinemas Sites are sponsored by third parties and you will be asked to submit personally identifiable information to complete your transaction. Additionally, Fandango.com and other ticketing sites are gathering customer information, including, but not limited to, credit card details on their web sites. Showcase Cinemas does not control how these third parties use the information they collect from you, whether collected from the delivery of advertisements to you, your use of links or your purchase of products or other voluntary submissions of information. Showcase Cinemas has no responsibility (and disclaims any representations, warranties or responsibility) for these third-party websites, including, without limitation, their content and privacy policies. Showcase Cinemas encourages you to read the privacy policies of these websites to learn how they may collect and use information about you.

**Access or Correction to Personally Identifiable Information**  
Showcase Cinemas retains your personally identifiable information for as long as you use an Application, remain a member of the Showcase Cinemas Starpass loyalty program, remain a member of the Showcase Subscribe membership program, or maintain an online account with a Showcase Cinemas Site, and for a reasonable time thereafter. Showcase Cinemas retains anonymous information it collects under this policy for up to twenty-three (23) days from the date of collection, and thereafter may only retain such information in the aggregate.  
You may obtain a copy of your personally identifiable information maintained by Showcase Cinemas by e-mailing us at [customer_service@national-amusements.com](mailto:customer_service@national-amusements.com "customer service"), or through direct mail at National Amusements, Inc., 846 University Avenue, PO Box 9108, Norwood, MA 02062-9108 Attn: Customer Service. For your protection, you will be required to provide proof of your identity to obtain a copy of your personally identifiable information. You may correct any errors in your personally identifiable information by providing Showcase Cinemas with the correct information. You may uninstall an Application from your mobile device at any time, and Showcase Cinemas will delete the personally identifiable information in its possession concerning your use of the Application; however, you will continue to receive e-mail communications if you selected that service through your account at a Showcase Cinemas Site. Showcase Cinemas will delete all of your personally identifiable information (except for your transaction history) from Showcase Cinemas’ records upon your written request. However, you will not be able to access some areas of the Showcase Cinemas Site, use some aspects of an Application or have an Application function properly if you choose to delete your personally identifiable information.

**How Do I Opt Out of Receiving Marketing Communications from Showcase Cinemas and Others?**  
When you create an account with Showcase Cinemas and during certain purchase transactions, you may opt out of receiving marketing communications from Showcase Cinemas. If you have an account with Showcase Cinemas, you may update your preferences concerning marketing communications at any time. You may also opt out of receiving communications from Showcase Cinemas by following the directions in Showcase Cinemas’ e-mail communication with you or by mailing your request, which must include your current contact information, to:  
National Amusements, Inc.  
846 University Ave  
PO Box 9108  
Norwood, MA 02062  
Showcase Cinemas will implement your request within a reasonable time. Please note that your request to opt out of receiving marketing communications will only apply to future communications and transactions with Showcase Cinemas. Even if you choose to opt out of receiving marketing communications from Showcase Cinemas, Showcase Cinemas will still send you transactional or administrative communications.

**Privacy for Children**  
In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, children (individuals 12 or under) may not subscribe to our e-mail service, enter contests or sweepstakes, join any clubs or programs or make purchases online. We encourage parents to supervise children’s online activities and review parent control tools available from online services to ensure a child-friendly experience on the Internet. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a child (individuals 12 or under), we will immediately purge that information. A parent or legal guardian of children (individuals 12 or under) can revoke the right to gather and/or use personally identifiable information of a child, and we will, upon such event, purge that information.  Such revocation will result in the termination of the affected child's participation in any programs. A parent or legal guardian may review your child's personally identifiable information at any time, and you may have your child’s information deleted at any time. To exercise these rights, please e-mail us at customer_service@national-amusements.com, National Amusements, Inc., 846 University Avenue, PO Box 9108, Norwood, MA, 02062-9108, Attn: Customer Service.  
The [“Popcorn Club” Online Privacy Policy](https://popcornclub.showcasecinemas.com/programs/kids-and-families/popcorn-club/privacy-policy "privacy policy") describes the practices specific to that program.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
Showcase Cinemas may change this privacy policy at any time. If Showcase Cinemas modifies this privacy policy to permit material changes in the way it collects uses and shares your personally identifiable information, it will affect the use and disclosure of information collected prior to the date of posting unless the modified privacy policy states otherwise. If you do not wish to allow such material changes, you must notify Showcase Cinemas in the manner Showcase Cinemas specifies prior to the effective date of the modification. If you provide Showcase Cinemas with this notice, Showcase Cinemas may choose to deactivate your online or Application account(s). Regardless of whether you provide Showcase Cinemas with notice, any modification to this privacy policy will apply to personally identifiable information you provide to Showcase Cinemas on or after the effective date of the modification.  
Your use of a Showcase Cinemas Site or an Application means that you accept the terms of this Policy and that Showcase Cinemas has the right to use information it collects from you, whether personally identifiable information or anonymous, as stated in this Policy. If you do not accept the terms of this Policy, you must not use the Showcase Cinemas Sites or Applications. Use of a Showcase Cinemas Site or an Application after a change to this Policy means that you accept the changes made to terms of this Policy. If you have any additional questions, please feel free to contact Showcase Cinemas any time at [customer_service@national-amusements.com](mailto:customer_service@national-amusements.com "customer_service").
